# **JAZMINE NGAJI**

Halifax, Nova Scotia | (902) 448-6684 jazminengaji@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/jazminengaji

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

An enthusiastic and skilled experienced Bookkeeper and Data Entry Specialist with strong analytical abilities with about three years experience in diverse industries including accounting firm, marketing, and manufacturing. Proficient in bookkeeping duties, including financial transaction recording, bank statement reconciliation, and tax filing preparation. My analytical skills allow me to identify trends and variances in financial data and generate informative reports that support informed decision-making, department initiatives, projects, and risk mitigation.

### **SKILLS**

Technical	Non- Technical	Tool / Software
✓ Excel (Power Query & Pivot & DAX)	✓ Adaptability	✓ QuickBooks
✓ Data Viz tools - Power BI, Tableau,	✓ Communication skil	lls ✓ Zoho Invoice
✓ Knowledge of Database System and	✓ Critical thinking skil	ls ✓ Base Camp
Warehouse - ETL	✓ Collaboration	✓ TurboTax
✓ Power BI & Tableau	✓ Time Management	✓ CRMs - HubSpot
✓ SQL Server Reporting Services	✓ Organizational skills	s ✓ DropBox
✓ SQL Language		

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Bookkeeper/ Data Entry Specialist | Andrew J Murphy CPA Inc | Halifax, NS

Nov 2022 - Current

- Manage and maintain client financial investment account statements, including tax filing and account management while meeting deadlines, handle multiple tasks simultaneously, and maintain confidential client information.
- Perform bookkeeping duties such as recording financial transactions, reconciling bank statements, and generating financial reports of client various investments and securities.
- Provide high-quality customer service to clients, responding to inquiries and addressing issues promptly and professionally.

**Tech. Business Analyst** | House of Dtechpreneur | Lagos, Nigeria

Feb 2021 - Aug 2022

- Revamped products and services through collaboration with stakeholders, fostering strong connections with clients, vendors, and stakeholders and boosting productivity by 15%.
- Conducted market research and trend analysis to stay current on industry developments and gather market intelligence.

- Assisted the team in identifying opportunities for improvement within client company operations and implemented solutions to support future growth and requirements.
- Created dashboards and reports for the CEO and Operations team to track key performance indicators (KPIs) and developed process flow diagrams.

## **Junior Data Analyst |** KALTANI Recycling Company | Lagos, Nigeria Jun 2021 - Feb 2022

- Ensured proper data management through the implementation of policies and quality data collection techniques, resulting in legitimate data exchange within the departments.
- Designed and implemented efficient and secure database systems to handle and analyze data, taking into consideration all technical aspects of the recycling machines.
- Assisted and updated reports and data as needed for proper analysis of any issues or problems that arose, leading to swift resolution.
- Monitored and analyzed information to assess performance and identified opportunities for improving processes in the recycling operations, resulting in reduced downtime by 10%.

### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES**

- Post Graduate Certificate, Business Intelligence Analytics | Nova Scotia Community College, Canada
- Transfer Credit (Hons), Business Administration | Ivey Business School, London, Ontario, Canada
- Bachelor of Engineering (Hons), Biomedical Engineering | All Nations University College, Ghana
- Bloomberg Market Concept | Bloomberg for Education

### **LEADERSHIP / VOLUTEER EXPERIENCE**

- Outreach Volunteer | Beatrice Arch. | Lagos, Nigeria
- Outreach Volunteer | All Nations University | Koforidua, Ghana
- Interim SRC President | All Nations University | Koforidua, Ghana

### **HONOURS/AWARDS**

Rahim Manji Bursary Awardee
 Ivey Business School, University of Western Ontario, Canada

Dec 2019 - Apr 2020

#### **REFERENCE**

Available Upon Request